oex.com 2016-09-15

# Prices - Polygamy.com

#### **What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or subscribe to our newsletter.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address or billing information.

#### **What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

; To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

; To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

; To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

; To process transactions  
(Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested)

; To send periodic emails  
(The email address you provide when registering with us, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your account, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc)

#### **How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you register, place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

All transactions are made by trusted third parties who implement the highest of security measures to keep your data safe and are PCI DSS compliant.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

#### **Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information)

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart and understand and save your preferences for future visits.

#### **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

#### **Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

#### **Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of our Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their account and going to the 'Edit Profile' page.

#### **Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 18 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 18 years old or older.

#### **Monitoring and moderating online activity**

Our members communicate with each other through onsite mail. In order to ensure that Islamic Principles of modesty are maintained we reserve the right to monitor these messages to see if any of our site terms have been broken. Member submissions that appear on the public area of the site are moderated and, if necessary, we reserve the right to edit, delete, remove or not use any communication on a public area of the site.

#### **Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website

#### **Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy.

#### **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and update the modification date.

* * *

This was last modified on 12 November, 2015
